Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Oversize
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Lamar Alexander Papers - Oversize
Undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0734
617 linear feet
- Series I: Early Years & Higher Education
  - Boy Scout Materials
    - Miscellaneous Badges, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Sashes and Handkerchiefs, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Boy Scout Uniform, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education
    - Hustler Volume 70, no. 9-29, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hustler Volume 71, no. 1-30, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education
    - Hustler Volume 72, no. 2-30, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Hustler Volume 73, no. 1-30, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Series II: Family Files
  - Family Files
    - Framed Flower Print – undated (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Framed Flower Print – undated (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series IV: Governor
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - T-shirts - alphabetical by county/city - Bledsoe – Greene (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified textile and red windbreaker “Alexander’s Band-Gran’mommy” (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - T-shirts – Alphabetical by county/city - Hamblen - Wilson (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - Buttons - “I’m Going the Extra Mile” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - Small Buttons “Come on Along Alexander” (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Small Guitar Stickers (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - Bumper stickers - “Alexander”; “I’m in Alexander’s Band” (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - Stationery and other (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Memorabilia (Large Flat Box)
    - Other items - stamps, counties of Tennessee map, and 45rpm vinyl recordings of inauguration (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Publicity (Flat Box)
    - Newspaper clippings, (February 28, 1982 - October 24, 1982) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Original artwork cartoon of Randy Tyree and Lamar Alexander by Bob Turner with newspaper cartoon clippings (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Series IX: Secretary of Education
  - Secretary of Education – Press and Publications, 1991-1992
    - NEA Today, 1991 May-June (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Parade Magazine, 1991 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Time Magazine, 1991 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Time Magazine, 1991 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Washington Times – “Education ‘91”, 1991 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1991 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Agenda, 1991 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - LA Times Magazine, 1992 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education, 1992
    - Welcome to Blythe Avenue School Scrapbook, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series X: Alexander for President, 1996
  - Campaign Items – “Lamar!” Large Flag – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Items – “Lamar!” Folding Sign – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Items – “Lamar!” Poster – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Items – “Come on along” Poster – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Items – “Come on along!” Poster – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Items – “Concord to Nashua to The Sea 1995-96 Walking Tour” Poster (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Items – “Now is the Time, Florida is the Place, Alexander is the One!” – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Items – “1-800-96-LAMAR” Sign – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Items – “Lamar!” Foamboard – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Items – Plastic Campaign Signs – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Items – “Lamar!” Black and Red Sign – circa, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)